(Penny:)Sheldon, it's just a box of rhinestones.
(Sheldon:)Contents are irrelevant.
A legal bailment has been created.
(Sheldon:)Does that mean nothing to you?
(Penny:)It means nothing to anybody.
(Penny:)- Let me show you what I'm doing.
- Bailment...
(Sheldon:)...describes a relationship
in common law...
(Sheldon:)...where a physical possession
of personal property, or chattels...
...is transferred from one person, the bailer,
to another person, the bailee.
(Penny:)Yeah, yeah. Look, look.
I started a business.
(Sheldon:)Obviously not a cleaning business.
(Penny:)No. I'm making flower barrettes. See?
(Penny:)I call them Penny Blossoms. I made one
for myself. All the girls at work wanted one.
(Penny:)I showed some to this lady who
runs a shop. She sells cards and jewelry.
(Penny:)She wanted to sell them, I said okay,
and in one week, I made a $156.
(Sheldon:)Good for you. Sign here.
(Penny:)Sheldon, don't you get it? If this takes off,
I won't have to be a waitress anymore.
(Sheldon:)But then who will bring me
my cheeseburger on Tuesday nights?
Another waitress?